I'm home!
Welcome home!
Ochugana, ochugana, ochugana, ochugana...
Oh, man!
So cute!
Ta-dai!
Oh!
Isn't that amazing?
Yeah!
Hello! I'm Kaho Fujishima from Hyugaizaka 46.
I'm here at New Chitose Airport.
Yay!
The reason why I'm here at New Chitose Airport is because last week at the 46-hour TV show, we had a surprise announcement that we would be making our first pitch to the Hokkaido Nippon Fighter's Fighters,
I am very nervous because the first pitch is scheduled for tomorrow, but I am going to enjoy Hokkaido to the fullest!
I have something to show you.
Ta-da!
I can do it!
Shibare Hokkaido!
I'm going to fully enjoy the Shibare Hokkaido from now on!
I'm going to visit my family!
I'm off to visit my family!
Have you had dinner yet?
I haven't eaten.
I have a dried sweet potato. I'm not sure if I want to eat it.
My baked potato.
I carry a dried sweet potato with me.
Don't you like sweet potatoes?
You like sweet potatoes.
I got sweet potatoes for money.
Oh, yeah, you got it for me.
He lit up the whole place.
Oh, look at that.
Oh, more!
Okay, I'll say hello to everyone.
Tane? Hold on.
Tane? What do you mean?
I'm home. I'm home!
I'm home!
I'm at my grandmother's house.
Oh, you're wearing a Hinatazaka T-shirt!
I can do it because Kaki's here.
I can do it.
Hinatazaka.
What's this one from?
What's this for?
Is it an album?
It looks like an album or an airport album.
They prepared dinner for us.
Good night.
There's a lot of nice food here.
Looks too good!
I'm going to have my favorite hot pot and a drink!
Seino, let's eat!
Hokkaido sashimi!
What is that color?
Black pepper!
We don't eat black pepper very often.
What is this color?
Black pepper
Japanese chikumi
I've never seen it before.
I just learned it on the plane.
I just learned it on a fox.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
I'm so nervous to watch.
But I'm also nervous about doing the choreography with you afterwards.
I didn't say I'd do it.
Oh, you're leaving?
You're going to make it?
Honey, honey, honey, honey, honey, honey.
That's good.
No, no, no, no, no. No, no, no.
You're gonna put your hair out?
I'm really confused.
I don't know. I just think it's a good idea.
I'm definitely going with that.
If I was a sheep...
I'd still let him take his hair out.
It's going to be my life.
I'm going to take a bath now.
I'm out of the bath!
HOKKAIDO
Well then, watch my wachigo-na dance!
I'll watch.
Ochigo-na, ochigo-na, ochigo-na, ochigo-na, ochigo-na.
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock.
Chitty, chitty, chitty.
Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man.
Here we go.
Fox dance.
Oh, yeah.
Come on.
Tottle ka nani nani nani
sah-sah-sah-sah-sah-sah-sah-sah-sah-sah-sah-sah-sah
what's in it for me?
wata-chi (Japanese traditional dance song)
Chitty, chitty, chitty, chitty, chitty.
Something like this.
There's “ahue ahue” and “ahue ahue” and so on.
Yes, there is.
Yay.
Good luck.
I'll have it perfect by tomorrow.
Well, lights out, then.
Good night.
Oh, my God.
No way.
She won't listen.
Bear won't listen.I'm not listening to you, bear.
I'm pulling.
Ah! Oh, thank God.
Good night.
I'm going to bed, bean.
Good morning.
Good evening
What's that?
Good evening.
Good morning.
It's morning. I overslept.
I was going to get up earlier.
Bread
We'll play catch in the park later.
What do you say?
Did you eat Pooh?
No, thanks. I'll have some eggs.
No need to be early.
It doesn't have to be fast.
It's all about control.
You don't have to be quick.
Oh, okay.
We all wore fighters' uniforms.
I did.
Fighters!
Let's go.
Fighters, let's go!
Here it comes! Where's 18 meters?
Still on his shoulder.
How cute is this?
It's here.
Isn't it amazing?
Isn't it great?
Yay.
Can we get some more?Maybe a little more?
This much?
Oh, shit!
I'm sorry.
So far.
I'm so nervous that I can't get my feet wet.
I'm so nervous that I can't keep my feet on the ground.
I'm moving forward like crazy.
I'm walking like crazy.
That's how I feel.
What are you doing?
Your hands are shaking.
They're shaking?
And you're breaking ku 00. Udon: !!!!
Try it again!
Thanks for your hard work.
Thanks for your hard work!
Oooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
wow!
That was awesome.
Was it amazing?
You were so cute!
I'm so happy.
I was kind of surprised at Kaho, but she was laughing while she was throwing the ball.
She was laughing?
I realized later when I saw the pictures, I thought she was throwing with a really damp face.
He was really throwing with a damp face, but he couldn't stop grinning when he was holding the ball.
I hope he had a really straight face at practice.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I was so uncomfortable at practice, and it didn't go well.
It's a little frustrating, really frustrating. It's pretty frustrating in that area.
It only took me 10 minutes.
About 15 minutes.
Strawberry crepe.Strawberry crepe, right?
Yum! This is yummy!
Woohoo, Woohoo!
Here it comes, here it comes.
We're back home!
I'd like to introduce you to the house.
I mean, I don't know if it's really a house introduction.
There's a picture of the brothers on the wall of the house.
This one is smaller than the other one.
It's of KAPHON.
You can see it in the photo.
They're totally different.
Not even close.
But when we take pictures, he always wears a Fighters T-shirt. It's amazing.
Hmm...
Okay, then.
I've prepared old albums and old letters, so I'm going to look at them now for the first time in a while,
I'll do that for sure.
I'm sure I will.
I wonder what she was making?
It's so cute.
Is this Mei-chan? No, it's not.
Isn't she saying “Mei-chan”?
Maybe it's Mei-chan Mei-chan.
Maybe this is Mei-chan's origami.
Maybe it's Mei-chan.
What about you, Mei-chan?
Yes, she is.
It's my favorite stuffed sheep from a long time ago.
Come here.
I'm looking forward to it.
He's so cute. He's so cute.
Oh, my God!
The kind that pops out.
The pop-up type. It's amazing.
It's all the rage.
It's so trendy, it's so trendy.
Oh my God, it's still in there, it's still in there. Oh, my God, it's still in there, it's still in there.
Did you know? I don't know.
I don't know.
It's too cute.
It's amazing.
It's so elaborate. I used to love how cute it was. I was kind of super crafty.
Oh, my God!
I love it.
It's so cute. It's so cute.
Oh, my God! I love it. Pink and red.
Oh, there it is. There it is. Let's put it on.
“Let's put it on.” I don't know what that means.
I don't know what that means. Do the chamois.
I don't know what you mean, “Let's wear it.” Do it, chamois.
Do it. Do it to my face.
It's so cute, isn't it? This moment... being let out by a train.
It's not cool that he's taking pictures.
It's so bad!
I'm taking pictures of you and your parents.
I'm so worried.
Good morning.
I'm on my way to the airport now.
I almost cried at Haneda Airport.
I've done that many times. Why at Haneda?
When I saw the airport, I thought I could go home, and I almost cried.
That camp was a little bit crazy, wasn't it? I was a bit nervous at that training camp, as expected. I cried on the plane. I was crying on the plane.
But, I don't know what it was, but I was crying on the plane,
Um, the woman next to me? There was a woman sitting next to me.
She was just, you know, next to me,
It's a pretty serious thing for a high school age girl to be crying.
Yeah, what happened?
There was a live concert that day in Hokkaido.
It was canceled.
So they definitely thought it was a girl who couldn't go to the concert.
Sure, like a girl, maybe.
Tamiya's player hee! That made you happy.
I was so happy!
I should have said “Hee!” last time. I should have said “Hee!” last time.I should have said “Hee hee!” last time. I should have just said “Hee!
Not one shutterbug-like moment.
That's where you were nervous.
I didn't have it in my head.
I'm glad you're happy.
You guys were so warm.
It was so warm.
I hope they call me back.
I'll do my best.
I have to work harder.
I arrived at Shintase Airport.
I've been in Hokkaido for 3 days, and I've realized how much I love Hokkaido.
And the time I spent with my family and the time I spent working in Hokkaido
I really treasure the time I spent with my family and the time I spent working in Hokkaido.
I will do my best so that I can come back to Hokkaido for work again!
Thank you for watching until the end!
Highly recommended!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Nama Ramen Love Hokkaido Bye bye!